pickrset.com 2010-11-22

# pickRset: Privacy Policy

## Effective October 30, 2007:

## About pickRset.com

PickRset.com is an online service that allows our members to set up personal profiles to vote on songs that they would like bands to play at concerts. PickRset members can view each others' profiles, share photos, and youtube.com videos. To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors. PickRset members can change their profile information at any time and can control how the service communicates with them.

## Information Collection and Use by pickRset.com

pickRset.com collects user submitted information such as name and email address to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the pickRset.com service. pickRset.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to bands they enjoy, music genres, and location in order to assist users in finding and communicating with bands.

pickRset.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the pickRset.com community. Users communicate on pickRset.com with bands through the pickRset.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members.

From time to time, pickRset.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on pickRset.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

## Use of Cookies

pickRset.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from pickRset.com in order to use most functions on the site Please note that pickRset allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the pickRset Privacy Policy. 

## Links

pickRset.com contains links to sites. pickRset.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on pickRset.com.

## Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

pickRset.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Basic Info and Change Password.

## Third Party Advertising

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by pickRset.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by pickRset.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Security

pickRset.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords pickRset.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.

## Sharing and Disclosure of Information pickRset.com Collects

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, pickRset will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by pickRset.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the pickRset.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. pickRset reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of pickRset or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [info@pickrset.com](mailto:info@pickrset.com)
